{"cards":[{"mId":"87797515-b861-415b-b463-6c2ea3dd067c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a distilled liquid such as rum or whiskey","mBack":"liquor"},{"mId":"aaa39d72-c774-4b19-b82f-7f037f970aa8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"small snack before a meal","mBack":"appetizer"},{"mId":"d8060238-b24d-43a9-abfd-748511eb8f2a","mCardType":"image","mFront":"d8060238-b24d-43a9-abfd-748511eb8f2a","mBack":"apron"},{"mId":"358925de-34f3-45e0-a633-a4da40d7d7a1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"place in an establishment where people go to get a drink (especially alcoholic drinks)","mBack":"bar"},{"mId":"1d8022a7-2ba1-4b20-8ab9-ec5007351a75","mCardType":"text","mFront":"southern style of cooking over a grill","mBack":"barbeque"},{"mId":"69463ba1-b2ee-42c0-afd4-7a0dbfea59c2","mCardType":"image","mFront":"69463ba1-b2ee-42c0-afd4-7a0dbfea59c2","mBack":"barstool"},{"mId":"e6b9970f-32de-42a0-ad44-0abffe87defe","mCardType":"text","mFront":"staff member that mixes, pours, and serves alcoholic beverages","mBack":"bartender"},{"mId":"b50b828b-eb59-41de-9aa5-849353b9b3ba","mCardType":"text","mFront":"drink","mBack":"beverage"},{"mId":"f34ac32e-1c42-4646-9973-d3e38615846b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"boilstyle of cooking that involves placing food in a deep pot of extremely hot water","mBack":"boil"},{"mId":"eed06bc9-4389-44ca-ba6f-5ee7e9fe4086","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a device used for opening beer bottles that don\u0027t twist off","mBack":"bottle opener"},{"mId":"733d99ff-5869-42bf-89eb-a036cec76174","mCardType":"image","mFront":"733d99ff-5869-42bf-89eb-a036cec76174","mBack":"bread basket"},{"mId":"9b7a4f0e-782d-43ca-b456-0abe945b1522","mCardType":"text","mFront":"self-serve tables of food that are set out for the customer to pick and choose from","mBack":"buffet"},{"mId":"c1a6901d-49b3-4ee5-84a7-9bb6f1c2b43b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"overcooked to the point of turning black","mBack":"burnt"},{"mId":"4a728bdb-8730-44f8-b8b4-55d8251d91b3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to add a fee","mBack":"charge"},{"mId":"18a76921-09eb-4932-9fec-0f8c6cf21094","mCardType":"text","mFront":"staff member who is professionally trained to prepare food","mBack":"chef"},{"mId":"f4c0370d-8a83-4ec4-a7e9-9cbe0a8e00dd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an alcoholic drink with juice","mBack":"cocktail"},{"mId":"57e5105e-4fa6-4d42-900b-38af419a1f96","mCardType":"text","mFront":"types of sauces that are added for flavouring (i.e. mustard)","mBack":"textcondiments"},{"mId":"2ebf8da6-40c2-4ad3-b598-49a6e3e3374a","mCardType":"image","mFront":"2ebf8da6-40c2-4ad3-b598-49a6e3e3374a","mBack":"corkscrew"},{"mId":"e84df9d8-26fa-4302-968f-5255d4fdd862","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a slip of paper that offers the customers a discounted rate","mBack":"coupon"},{"mId":"0b04f46a-d635-4917-9f94-d13d48265649","mCardType":"text","mFront":"free of charge","mBack":"complimentary"},{"mId":"710335d5-707b-4c77-8e98-0342e744b733","mCardType":"text","mFront":"small plastic container of cream for coffee","mBack":"creamer"},{"mId":"fa3122cf-b4f8-48b1-81e4-1f99ffc8ec52","mCardType":"image","mFront":"fa3122cf-b4f8-48b1-81e4-1f99ffc8ec52","mBack":"cutlery"},{"mId":"72b602c0-57d6-4a49-887a-f19661c0b53b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cooked in a large pot of oil","mBack":"deep fried"},{"mId":"f3580240-2d28-458f-8201-5dbf42adfa40","mCardType":"text","mFront":"remove frozen food from the freezer to prepare","mBack":"defrost"},{"mId":"b1a6f139-ba29-4822-b6d5-3eca0d68a8a7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"sweet treat after a meal","mBack":"dessert"},{"mId":"e6ab6cbe-2d0f-4b16-91d8-b509aa4ccd97","mCardType":"text","mFront":"unfinished food that is packed up for the customer to take home","mBack":"doggie bag"},{"mId":"61136b21-a168-435b-b2e3-6ce68f51e53c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"beer from a keg that pours out of a tap","mBack":"draft"},{"mId":"ee5c7464-317c-487a-9f1a-c5e0072cf4fd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"main course","mBack":"entrée"},{"mId":"752ab4f1-4dfc-4e08-977b-96e21491cef0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cook over an element in oil","mBack":"fry"},{"mId":"aeb80006-1db4-444e-8850-599a4be85f8b","mCardType":"image","mFront":"aeb80006-1db4-444e-8850-599a4be85f8b","mBack":"garnish"},{"mId":"a61b98a0-7ad3-4d80-960a-2ac5e97797c1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"extra money given as a thank you for service","mBack":"tip"},{"mId":"4b7c9d87-6804-4311-9dfc-6b337caa32b5","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cooking over iron slats that allow for oil and fat to drop down","mBack":"grill"},{"mId":"74e0613d-8671-4468-9736-e66b52b4c3fb","mCardType":"text","mFront":"alcohol that has a syrupy/sweet taste","mBack":"liqueur"},{"mId":"1ef61f00-711f-41b9-bf17-e1771abefdf3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"warm to soften (i.e. cheese/butter)","mBack":"melt"},{"mId":"9776e68c-7bc0-4bd1-9d48-7e32e46f304f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a booklet of all of the food that can be ordered","mBack":"menu"},{"mId":"ef19b83b-13c2-4ff8-99db-bfbcc7268d51","mCardType":"text","mFront":"not spicy","mBack":"mild"},{"mId":"62450be9-951e-4691-a911-765a7ea670a7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"outdoor seeating","mBack":"patio"},{"mId":"7c4b308d-cb24-4ab0-9e79-c4a089efd425","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a separate amount of food","mBack":"portion"},{"mId":"2537b68b-e972-4858-85d7-5064b930682b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"establishment that specializes in casual food and alcoholic beverages","mBack":"pub"},{"mId":"6c178f95-9b4a-4b6f-9d3a-0c3eea0dfa6e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cooked meat that is pink inside","mBack":"rare"},{"mId":"4b047133-043e-42de-98e2-5f815f2f9dc6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"list of ingredients and instructions for preparing a certain type of food","mBack":"recipe"},{"mId":"a0a06863-b110-4c62-a824-3f9edfc5cd00","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a request to have a table saved for a certain amount of people","mBack":"reservation"},{"mId":"3ba6d10d-ec79-44a8-a0d8-9bce9a709595","mCardType":"text","mFront":"liquid flavouring added to food","mBack":"sauce"},{"mId":"1c07b8b6-39d3-488d-8bc6-57d79d16518b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"choice of food that goes with a main meal","mBack":"side dish"},{"mId":"53cacac2-ab15-4773-ad96-b30509529a71","mCardType":"text","mFront":"acid or fermented taste","mBack":"sour"},{"mId":"657380b7-a774-4676-afa0-87821df56cea","mCardType":"text","mFront":"hot flavour","mBack":"spicy"},{"mId":"43996ec0-5052-4e68-9f66-1f47314175bb","mCardType":"text","mFront":"long hollow plastic stick for drinking out of","mBack":"straw"},{"mId":"f737cbc8-94cb-4591-ba92-e922ab83d66c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"taste with a lot of sugar","mBack":"sweet"},{"mId":"b01601b0-bc94-49db-b3c9-f42f0e706165","mCardType":"text","mFront":"food items that go on top of other food items to add flavour","mBack":"toppings"}]}